Maxcine Blunt

Spa Host - MGM Spa and Salon

Fort Washington, MD 20744 maxaineblunt13@gmail.com 240-501-1109

I am an accomplished and energetic customer service advisor with a solid history of achievement in communication and marketing. Motivated leader with strong organizational and prioritization abilities. Areas of expertise include sales and marketing, customer personal service and critical thinking

Work Experience

Spa Host

MGM Spa and Salon - Oxon Hill, MD December 2017 to April 2018

- -Consistently offer professional, friendly and engaging service
- -Assist in the operation of all spa departments and to have knowledge of all Spa treatments
- -Maintain linen inventory to and from laundry on a scheduled basis
- -Direct Members and Guests to appointments and assist them with the use of sauna, steam, roman tub.
- -Prepare rooms for treatments according to specified
- -Prepare rooms for treatments according to specified guidelines
- -Maintain the facility in peak sanitary condition at all times and report any equipment deficiencies
- -Maintain locker rooms in a tidy manner and ensure all amenities are stocked
- -Follow departmental policies and procedures
- -Follow all safety and sanitation policies
- -Other duties such as spa and salon tours and walk throughs

Sales Associate

Gymboree - Oxon Hill, MD October 2017 to January 2018

- -Prepare sales slips or sales contracts.
- -Help customers try on or fit merchandise.
- -Welcome customers to the store and answer their queries
- -Maintain knowledge of current sales and promotions, policies regarding payment and exchanges, and security practices.

- -Maintain in-stock and presentable condition assigned areas
- -Take stock inventory
- -Watch for and recognize security risks and thefts, and know how to prevent or handle these situations.
- -Open and close cash registers, performing tasks such as counting money, separating charge slips, coupons, and

vouchers, balancing cash drawers, and making deposits.

Sales Associate

Children's Place - Oxon Hill, MD August 2017 to January 2018

- -Working closely with customers to determine their needs,
- answer their questions about our products and recommend the right solutions
- -Ensure high levels of customer satisfaction through

excellent sales service

- -Welcome customers to the store and answer their queries
- -Follow and achieve department's sales goals on a monthly, quarterly and yearly basis
- -Maintain in stock and presentable condition assigned

areas

- -Actively seek out customers in store
- -Remain knowledgeable on products offered and discuss

available options

- -Process POS purchases
- -Cross sell products
- -Handle returns of merchandise
- -Team up with co-workers to ensure proper customer service
- -Build productive trust relationships with customers
- -Comply with inventory control procedures

Director of First Impressions- Receptionist

8 Fine Men's Salon - Bethesda, MD August 2016 to January 2017

- -Resolve customer complaints regarding sales and service.
- -Direct, coordinate, and review activities in sales and service accounting and recordkeeping, and in receiving and

shipping operations.

- -Operate telephone switchboard to answer, screen, or forward calls, providing information, taking messages, or
- scheduling appointments.
- -Greet persons entering establishment, determine nature and purpose of visit, and direct or escort them to specific destinations.
- -Receive and record receipts for services.
- -Perform duties, such as taking care of plants or straightening magazines to maintain lobby or reception

area and dusting retail shelves.

-Keep records of customer interactions or transactions, recording details of inquiries, complaints, or comments, as well as actions taken.

-Creates and prints fax cover sheets, memos, correspondence, reports, and other documents when necessary

Girl Empowerment Mentor

Joy of Motion - Washington, DC June 2015 to August 2015

- -Senior Mentor for teens 15 and younger
- -Counsel individuals to help them understand and overcome personal, social, or behavioral problems affecting

their educational or vocational situations.

-Provide crisis intervention to students when difficult situations occur at schools.

Education

Prince George's Community College - Largo, MD August 2017 to Present

Roosevelt STAY High School - Washington, DC August 2016 to June 2017

McKinley Technology High School - Washington, DC

August 2013 to June 2016

Skills

Host